[{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664498422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":30309,"timeElapsed":94318},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664507079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8656,"timeElapsed":102976},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664516002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8922,"timeElapsed":111899},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4223,"timeElapsed":116123},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664528194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7973,"timeElapsed":124091},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5262,"timeElapsed":129354},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664536413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2955,"timeElapsed":132310},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664546733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":10320,"timeElapsed":142630},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664554085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7352,"timeElapsed":149982},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664575161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":19767,"timeElapsed":171058},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664585614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":10458,"timeElapsed":181511},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664613340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":27725,"timeElapsed":209237},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664618462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5121,"timeElapsed":214359},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664624956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6493,"timeElapsed":220853},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664627595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":223492},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664629816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2220,"timeElapsed":225713},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664638025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":8209,"timeElapsed":233922},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":237218},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664653960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":10917,"timeElapsed":249857},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664658844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4883,"timeElapsed":254741},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664669224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10380,"timeElapsed":265121},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664672031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2806,"timeElapsed":267928},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664675369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3338,"timeElapsed":271266},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664679986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4616,"timeElapsed":275883},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664683438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3452,"timeElapsed":279335},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9411,"timeElapsed":288747},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664694594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1744,"timeElapsed":290491},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664707990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":12347,"timeElapsed":303887},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664712339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4353,"timeElapsed":308236},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664718784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6444,"timeElapsed":314681},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664721441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2657,"timeElapsed":317338},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664725421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3980,"timeElapsed":321318},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664728528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3106,"timeElapsed":324425},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664730645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2116,"timeElapsed":326542},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664737160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6515,"timeElapsed":333057},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664740415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3254,"timeElapsed":336312},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664752940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8621,"timeElapsed":348837},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":351478},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664761571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5990,"timeElapsed":357468},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664764000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2428,"timeElapsed":359897},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664766552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2552,"timeElapsed":362449},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664768596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":364493},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664770764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2167,"timeElapsed":366661},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664774671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":370568},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664777064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2392,"timeElapsed":372961},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664791667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":13447,"timeElapsed":387564},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664793333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1665,"timeElapsed":389230},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664796759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3426,"timeElapsed":392656},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664799165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2405,"timeElapsed":395062},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664804077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4912,"timeElapsed":399974},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664807552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3474,"timeElapsed":403449},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664809449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1896,"timeElapsed":405346},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664811242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1792,"timeElapsed":407139},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664816832,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5590,"timeElapsed":412729},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664822872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6040,"timeElapsed":418769},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664829283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5424,"timeElapsed":425180},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664831819,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2540,"timeElapsed":427716},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664835880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4061,"timeElapsed":431777},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664839433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3552,"timeElapsed":435330},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664844824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5390,"timeElapsed":440721},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664847774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2949,"timeElapsed":443671},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664850753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2978,"timeElapsed":446650},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664853691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2938,"timeElapsed":449588},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664859130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5439,"timeElapsed":455027},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664860461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1330,"timeElapsed":456358},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664869859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8401,"timeElapsed":465756},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664872698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2838,"timeElapsed":468595},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664874931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2233,"timeElapsed":470828},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664876800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1868,"timeElapsed":472697},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664879939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3138,"timeElapsed":475836},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664884200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4260,"timeElapsed":480097},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664886359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2159,"timeElapsed":482256},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664889933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3573,"timeElapsed":485830},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664891252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1323,"timeElapsed":487149},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664913162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":20802,"timeElapsed":509059},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664914770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1608,"timeElapsed":510667},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664917707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2936,"timeElapsed":513604},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664919973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2266,"timeElapsed":515870},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664922244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":518141},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664924001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1757,"timeElapsed":519898},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664926050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2048,"timeElapsed":521947},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664927996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1946,"timeElapsed":523893},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664929251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1255,"timeElapsed":525148},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664940235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10168,"timeElapsed":536132},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664942077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1841,"timeElapsed":537974},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664945354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3277,"timeElapsed":541251},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664947409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":543306},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664949434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":545331},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664952768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3338,"timeElapsed":548665},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664954528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1759,"timeElapsed":550425},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664956335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":552232},{"subjectID":"k6cn9swe85","prolificID":"66c4a32221f616ebf48ab21d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421675ed9fd105ed4f47c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664957548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1212,"timeElapsed":553445}]